<airports>
	<airport>
		<name>Ben Gurion Airport</name>
		<code>LLBG</code>
		<location>Tel Aviv</location>
		<description>Ben Gurion Airport, located in Tel Aviv, is the main international airport in
			Israel. It serves as a major hub for both domestic and international flights, offering a
			wide range of passenger and cargo services.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Haifa Airport</name>
		<code>LLHA</code>
		<location>Haifa</location>
		<description>Haifa Airport in Israel is a modern transportation hub with top-notch
			facilities and a well-connected infrastructure, serving domestic and international
			travelers. It offers convenient access to Haifa city, coastal areas, tourist
			attractions, and business centers, providing a pleasant journey that meets international
			safety standards.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Eilat Airport</name>
		<code>LLET</code>
		<location>Eilat</location>
		<description>Eilat Airport is a regional airport located in the southern city of Eilat,
			Israel. It serves as a gateway to the popular resort destination, offering convenient
			access to pristine beaches, vibrant nightlife, and outdoor activities. With modern
			facilities and efficient services, Eilat Airport ensures a pleasant travel experience
			for visitors exploring the enchanting attractions of the region.</description>
	</airport>

	<airport>
		<name>Ramon Airport</name>
		<code>LLER</code>
		<location>Eilat</location>
		<description>Ramon Airport, located near the city of Eilat in southern Israel, is a modern
			transportation hub for domestic and international travelers. Surrounded by breathtaking
			desert landscapes, it offers advanced facilities and comprehensive infrastructure,
			providing easy access to the vibrant city of Eilat, coastal areas, tourist attractions,
			recreational activities, and business centers. With a commitment to customer
			satisfaction and international safety standards, Ramon Airport ensures a pleasant and
			convenient journey for all passengers, enhancing the overall travel experience in the
			region.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Herzliya Airport</name>
		<code>LLHZ</code>
		<location>Herzliya</location>
		<description>Herzliya Airport, conveniently located in the beautiful city of Herzliya,
			Israel, serves as a modern and efficient transportation hub for both domestic and
			international travelers. Situated near the picturesque Mediterranean coastline, the
			airport offers a seamless and convenient travel experience, featuring state-of-the-art
			facilities and a well-connected infrastructure. With a variety of airlines and
			destinations, Herzliya Airport acts as a gateway to the captivating city of Herzliya and
			its surrounding areas, providing easy access to popular tourist attractions, luxurious
			resorts, and thriving business centers. Committed to ensuring customer satisfaction and
			upholding international safety standards, Herzliya Airport guarantees a pleasant and
			hassle-free journey for all passengers, contributing to an exceptional travel experience
			in the region.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Rosh Pina Airport</name>
		<code>LLIB</code>
		<location>Rosh Pina</location>
		<description>Rosh Pina Airport, situated in the serene town of Rosh Pina in northern Israel,
			is a quaint yet efficient transportation hub catering to domestic and international
			travelers. Surrounded by picturesque landscapes and nestled in the Galilee region, the
			airport offers a seamless and enjoyable travel experience with its modern facilities and
			well-maintained infrastructure. Despite its smaller size, Rosh Pina Airport provides
			convenient access to various airlines and destinations, acting as a gateway to the
			charming town of Rosh Pina and the nearby attractions such as the Sea of Galilee and the
			Golan Heights. Committed to passenger satisfaction and adhering to stringent safety
			protocols, Rosh Pina Airport ensures a pleasant and hassle-free journey, contributing to
			the overall travel experience in the region.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Arad Airfield</name>
		<code>LLAR</code>
		<location>Arad</location>
		<description>Arad Airfield, located in the city of Arad in southern Israel, is a small yet
			vital aviation facility catering to various aviation needs. With its strategic location
			in the Negev Desert, the airfield serves as an important hub for private and
			recreational aviation activities. While not designated as an international airport, Arad
			Airfield offers essential services and facilities for general aviation enthusiasts,
			including flight training, aerial tours, and aerial sports. The airfield's serene
			surroundings and unique desert landscape provide an ideal backdrop for flying
			experiences. Committed to safety and serving the local aviation community, Arad Airfield
			contributes to the overall aviation experience in the region, making it a popular
			destination for flying enthusiasts and pilots.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Bar Yehuda Airfield</name>
		<code>LLMZ</code>
		<location>Masada</location>
		<description>Bar Yehuda Airfield, located near the historic site of Masada in southern
			Israel, is a small but important airfield catering to various aviation needs. Situated
			in the breathtaking Judean Desert, the airfield offers a unique and scenic flying
			experience. While not classified as an international airport, Bar Yehuda Airfield
			provides essential services and facilities for general aviation, including private
			flights, aerial tours, and skydiving operations. The airfield's proximity to the iconic
			Masada fortress and the stunning Dead Sea region makes it a popular destination for
			tourists seeking aerial views of these historical and natural wonders. Committed to
			safety and supporting aviation activities in the area, Bar Yehuda Airfield contributes
			to the overall aviation experience, providing unforgettable flying adventures in a truly
			remarkable setting.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Be'er Sheva Teyman Airfield</name>
		<code>LLBS</code>
		<location>Be'er Sheva</location>
		<description>Be'er Sheva Teyman Airfield, located in the city of Be'er Sheva in southern
			Israel, is a regional airfield serving various aviation needs. Situated in the heart of
			the Negev Desert, the airfield offers a unique flying experience with its vast open
			spaces and stunning desert landscapes. While not classified as an international airport,
			Be'er Sheva Teyman Airfield provides essential services for general aviation, including
			flight training, aerial photography, and private flights. The airfield's strategic
			location in Be'er Sheva makes it a convenient choice for local aviation enthusiasts and
			small aircraft operators in the region. Committed to safety and supporting the local
			aviation community, Be'er Sheva Teyman Airfield contributes to the overall aviation
			experience, providing a gateway to exploring the beauty of the Negev Desert from the
			skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Ein Shemer Airfield</name>
		<code>LLES</code>
		<location>Ein Shemer</location>
		<description>Ein Shemer Airfield, situated in the town of Ein Shemer in northern Israel, is
			a regional airfield catering to various aviation needs. Nestled amidst the picturesque
			landscapes of the Jezreel Valley, the airfield offers a scenic and pleasant flying
			experience. While not classified as an international airport, Ein Shemer Airfield
			provides essential services for general aviation, including flight training, private
			flights, and recreational flying. The airfield's strategic location in the heart of
			agricultural and rural areas makes it an ideal base for aerial activities and
			sightseeing tours over the lush countryside. Committed to safety and supporting the
			local aviation community, Ein Shemer Airfield contributes to the overall aviation
			experience, providing an opportunity to explore the beauty of northern Israel from the
			skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Ein Vered Airfield</name>
		<code>LLEV</code>
		<location>Ein Vered</location>
		<description>Ein Vered Airfield, located in the village of Ein Vered in central Israel, is a
			regional airfield serving various aviation needs. Surrounded by beautiful rural
			landscapes, the airfield offers a serene and inviting flying experience. While not
			classified as an international airport, Ein Vered Airfield provides essential services
			for general aviation, including flight training, private flights, and recreational
			flying. The airfield's convenient location in central Israel makes it a convenient
			choice for local aviation enthusiasts and small aircraft operators. With its commitment
			to safety and supporting the local aviation community, Ein Vered Airfield contributes to
			the overall aviation experience, providing a gateway to exploring the charm of the
			Israeli countryside from the skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Ein Yahav-Sapir Airfield</name>
		<code>LLEY</code>
		<location>Ein Yahav-Sapir</location>
		<description>Ein Yahav-Sapir Airfield, situated in the community of Ein Yahav-Sapir in
			southern Israel, is a regional airfield catering to various aviation needs. Surrounded
			by the breathtaking landscapes of the Arava Valley, the airfield offers a unique and
			picturesque flying experience. While not classified as an international airport, Ein
			Yahav-Sapir Airfield provides essential services for general aviation, including flight
			training, private flights, and recreational flying. The airfield's strategic location
			near the Arava region, known for its desert beauty and nature reserves, makes it an
			ideal base for aviation activities and aerial exploration of the area. Committed to
			safety and supporting the local aviation community, Ein Yahav-Sapir Airfield contributes
			to the overall aviation experience, providing a gateway to discover the stunning
			landscapes of southern Israel from the skies.</description>


	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Fik Airfield</name>
		<code>LLFK</code>
		<location>Fik</location>
		<description>Fik Airfield, located in the village of Fik in northern Israel, is a small
			regional airfield serving various aviation needs. Nestled amidst the beautiful
			landscapes of the Upper Galilee region, the airfield offers a scenic and tranquil flying
			experience. While not classified as an international airport, Fik Airfield provides
			essential services for general aviation, including flight training, private flights, and
			recreational flying. The airfield's convenient location in the Galilee makes it a
			preferred choice for local aviation enthusiasts and small aircraft operators. With its
			commitment to safety and supporting the local aviation community, Fik Airfield
			contributes to the overall aviation experience, providing an opportunity to explore the
			charm of northern Israel from the skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Habonim Airfield</name>
		<code>LLBO</code>
		<location>Habonim</location>
		<description>Habonim Airfield, situated in the community of Habonim in western Israel, is a
			regional airfield catering to various aviation needs. Located near the stunning
			Mediterranean coastline, the airfield offers a picturesque and enjoyable flying
			experience. While not classified as an international airport, Habonim Airfield provides
			essential services for general aviation, including flight training, private flights, and
			recreational flying. The airfield's proximity to the Mediterranean Sea and the beautiful
			beaches makes it a desirable destination for aviation enthusiasts and pilots looking to
			enjoy coastal flying. Committed to safety and supporting the local aviation community,
			Habonim Airfield contributes to the overall aviation experience, providing an
			opportunity to explore the scenic wonders of western Israel from the skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Kiryat Shmona Airport</name>
		<code>LLKS</code>
		<location>Kiryat Shmona</location>
		<description>Kiryat Shmona Airport, located in the city of Kiryat Shmona in northern Israel,
			is a regional airport serving both domestic and limited international flights. Nestled
			amidst the scenic landscapes of the Upper Galilee region, the airport offers a
			convenient and efficient travel experience. With its well-maintained facilities and
			infrastructure, Kiryat Shmona Airport provides essential services for passenger flights,
			cargo operations, and general aviation. Serving as a gateway to the picturesque Galilee
			region, the airport offers access to popular tourist destinations, hiking trails, and
			historical sites. Committed to safety and customer satisfaction, Kiryat Shmona Airport
			ensures a pleasant and hassle-free journey, contributing to the overall travel
			experience in northern Israel.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Megiddo Airfield</name>
		<code>LLMG</code>
		<location>Megiddo</location>
		<description>Megiddo Airfield, located near the historic site of Megiddo in northern Israel,
			is a small regional airfield catering to various aviation needs. Surrounded by the
			scenic landscapes of the Jezreel Valley, the airfield offers a pleasant and convenient
			flying experience. While not classified as an international airport, Megiddo Airfield
			provides essential services for general aviation, including flight training, private
			flights, and recreational flying. The airfield's strategic location near Megiddo, known
			for its archaeological significance and natural beauty, makes it an ideal base for
			aviation activities and aerial exploration of the region. Committed to safety and
			supporting the local aviation community, Megiddo Airfield contributes to the overall
			aviation experience, providing an opportunity to discover the historical and natural
			wonders of northern Israel from the skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Mitzpe Ramon Airfield</name>
		<code>LLMR</code>
		<location>Mitzpe Ramon</location>
		<description>Mitzpe Ramon Airfield, located in the town of Mitzpe Ramon in southern Israel,
			is a small regional airfield catering to various aviation needs. Situated near the
			majestic Ramon Crater, the airfield offers a unique and awe-inspiring flying experience.
			While not classified as an international airport, Mitzpe Ramon Airfield provides
			essential services for general aviation, including flight training, private flights, and
			recreational flying. The airfield's proximity to the Ramon Crater, a geological wonder
			and popular tourist attraction, makes it an ideal base for aviation enthusiasts and
			pilots looking to explore the breathtaking desert landscapes from above. Committed to
			safety and supporting the local aviation community, Mitzpe Ramon Airfield contributes to
			the overall aviation experience, providing an opportunity to witness the natural beauty
			of southern Israel from the skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Rishon LeZion Airfield</name>
		<code>LLRS</code>
		<location>Rishon LeZion</location>
		<description>Rishon LeZion Airfield, located in the city of Rishon LeZion in central Israel,
			is a regional airfield serving various aviation needs. Situated near the bustling
			metropolitan area of Tel Aviv, the airfield offers convenient access to urban and
			suburban destinations. While not classified as an international airport, Rishon LeZion
			Airfield provides essential services for general aviation, including flight training,
			private flights, and recreational flying. The airfield's strategic location near Tel
			Aviv, a major economic and cultural hub, makes it an ideal choice for local aviation
			enthusiasts and small aircraft operators. With its commitment to safety and supporting
			the local aviation community, Rishon LeZion Airfield contributes to the overall aviation
			experience, providing a gateway to explore the dynamic and vibrant region of central
			Israel from the skies.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Tnuvot Airfield</name>
		<code>LLTN</code>
		<location>Tnuvot</location>
		<description>Tnuvot Airfield is a regional airfield located in the town of Tnuvot in
			southern Israel. Serving general aviation needs, it offers flight training, private
			flights, and recreational flying. Situated in a scenic area, Tnuvot Airfield provides a
			pleasant flying experience in the southern region of the country.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Yotvata Airfield</name>
		<code>LLYO</code>
		<location>Yotvata</location>
		<description>Yotvata Airfield, located in the community of Yotvata in southern Israel, is a
			regional airfield catering to general aviation needs. Offering flight training, private
			flights, and recreational flying, it provides a convenient and accessible option for
			aviation enthusiasts. Situated in a picturesque desert setting, Yotvata Airfield offers
			a unique flying experience amidst the stunning landscapes of southern Israel.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Hatzerim Airbase</name>
		<code>LLHB</code>
		<location>Hatzerim</location>
		<description>Hatzerim Airbase, with the ICAO code LLHB, is a military airbase located in
			Hatzerim, southern Israel. Serving as the main base for the Israeli Air Force, it plays
			a vital role in national defense and security. Equipped with advanced facilities and
			infrastructure, Hatzerim Airbase supports various military aircraft operations, training
			exercises, and defense missions, ensuring the readiness and capabilities of the Israeli
			Air Force.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Hatzor Airbase</name>
		<code>LLHS</code>
		<location>Hatzor</location>
		<description>Hatzor Airbase, with the ICAO code LLHS, is a significant military airbase
			located in Hatzor, central Israel. As a key operational base for the Israeli Air Force,
			it plays a crucial role in national defense and security. Equipped with advanced
			facilities and infrastructure, Hatzor Airbase supports a wide range of military aircraft
			operations, including training, tactical missions, and strategic deployments, ensuring
			the readiness and capabilities of the Israeli Air Force in safeguarding the nation.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Nevatim Airbase</name>
		<code>LLNV</code>
		<location>Nevatim</location>
		<description>Nevatim Airbase, with the ICAO code LLNV, is a major military airbase located
			in Nevatim, southern Israel. Serving as a key operational base for the Israeli Air
			Force, it plays a vital role in national defense and security. Equipped with
			state-of-the-art facilities and infrastructure, Nevatim Airbase supports various
			military aircraft operations, including training, combat missions, and strategic
			deployments, contributing to the defense capabilities of the Israeli Air Force and
			ensuring the protection of the nation.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Ramat David Airbase</name>
		<code>LLRD</code>
		<location>Ramat David</location>
		<description>Ramat David Airbase, located in the town of Ramat David, is a significant
			military airbase in northern Israel. It serves as a crucial operational base for the
			Israeli Air Force, supporting various missions and training exercises. Equipped with
			advanced facilities and infrastructure, Ramat David Airbase plays a vital role in
			national defense and security, ensuring the readiness and capabilities of the Israeli
			Air Force in safeguarding the country.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Ramon Airbase</name>
		<code>LLRM</code>
		<location>Ramon</location>
		<description>Ramon Airbase, located in Ramon, southern Israel, is a major military airbase.
			Serving as a key operational hub for the Israeli Air Force, it plays a critical role in
			national defense and security. Equipped with state-of-the-art facilities and
			infrastructure, Ramon Airbase supports various military aircraft operations, including
			training, combat missions, and strategic deployments, ensuring the readiness and
			capabilities of the Israeli Air Force in protecting the country.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Tel Nof Airbase</name>
		<code>LLEK</code>
		<location>Tel Nof</location>
		<description>Tel Nof Airbase, with the ICAO code LLEK, is a major military airbase located
			in Tel Nof, central Israel. Serving as a critical operational base for the Israeli Air
			Force, it plays a pivotal role in national defense and security. Equipped with advanced
			facilities and infrastructure, Tel Nof Airbase supports various military aircraft
			operations, including training, combat missions, and strategic deployments, ensuring the
			readiness and capabilities of the Israeli Air Force in safeguarding the nation.</description>
	</airport>
	<airport>
		<name>Uvda Airport</name>
		<code>LLOV</code>
		<location>Uvda</location>
		<description>Uvda Airport, with the ICAO code LLOV, is a regional airport located in Uvda,
			southern Israel. It serves as a gateway to the popular tourist destination of Eilat and
			the surrounding area. With its modern facilities and convenient access to the Red Sea
			resort city, Uvda Airport provides domestic and international travelers with a seamless
			travel experience. Whether for leisure or business, the airport offers a range of
			services and connections to accommodate the needs of passengers visiting the beautiful
			southern region of Israel.</description>
	</airport>


</airports>